- Previously on
"The Bachelorette"...
[both shouting]
- Luke can't control himself.
He's an unstable guy.
He shouldn't be here.
You know everyone in here
thinks you're nuts, right?
- You're violent,
you're aggressive,
you laugh because you're
a [bleep] psychopath.
- I'm a competitor and I'm
gonna do everything I can
to fight for Hannah's heart.
Luke's always talking about
his brand
and his liquor company
and I've never heard him
talk about you.
- I'm pissed off Luke P.
will say anything
to save his own skin.
I'm here for Hannah,
and don't you forget it.
- Last night was really hard.
I'm just struggling
with my emotions.
- She doesn't trust me.
Please go up there
and tell her the truth.
- Yeah, I plan on it.
Luke S. came up to me
asking me to put in
a good word for him.
- It doesn't make sense.
I'm confused but also like
irritated because I just, like,
don't know who to trust.
- Karma is a bitch,
and you're gonna get yours.
- I need to get to the bottom
of everything.
Luke and Luke,
can I talk to y'all?
- It's time for Luke P.
and Luke S. to go home.
- The drama continues
on "The Bachelorette,"
starting right now.
- What are we gonna do
if Luke S. goes home
and Luke P. stays?
- We just all have to be
really careful in this.
He will do anything to rise up.
He'll pull anyone down.
He's not a good dude.
He's proven it over
and over again.
- We're at the cocktail
party tonight.
And the Luke P. thing
came up again.
I'm tired of hearing
about the Luke S.
and Luke P. situation,
honestly.
- Someone's definitely
getting sent home
because of this [bleep].
- I think one of them.
- Hope Luke S. stays.
Hope Luke--Luke P. gets
the hell out of here.
- I still haven't talked
to Hannah yet
and it is frustrating.
If I don't see her tonight,
um, I could be going home.
She's mainly focused
on both Lukes
trying to get clarity
of what's going on
between those two.
So, yeah, it sucks.
- She's a tough cookie
and she means business.
I trust that in the end
she'll make the right call.
- Y'all have both talked
to me separately,
but I just, like,
am really confused,
so I just want to hear you both
talk to each other about this.
Like, what's going on?
- Uh...
Luke P. said a--
- No, not--not to me.
To him.
- Okay.
Uh, Luke, you made up
a bold-faced lie about me
promoting, uh,
my tequila company,
which doesn't even exist yet.
Um, you decided to tell Hannah
in order to sabotage
my relationship with her.
And then after I trust that
you're gonna go to Hannah
and s--and clear
the air with her,
you then go to her
and say that I forced you
basically to go talk to her.
- You had strongly advised me
to go talk to her
about what I think
is the truth.
- If you phrase it to Hannah--
- Let me--wait.
Let me--let me--let me explain
something real quick.
- That I forced you
to go do that,
she's clearly going
to be upset with me.
- Let me explain
something real quick.
- Do you understand that?
- Let me explain to you
something real quick.
You did express to me that you
are here for the right reasons.
And I had already told Hannah
the other night
that I don't believe you are.
I'm not gonna sit here
and ever tell Hannah
anything that I don't believe.
If I feel a certain way,
I'm gonna express that to her.
- Why--why do you believe
that I'm not here
for the right reasons?
- You know, I just don't see
a fit for Hannah.
- Oh, so you're speaking
for her now?
- No, no, no, no, no.
I'm just going based off
what she's expressed to us
and what I've perceived
from you.
Did you or did you not...
- I said to you--
- Tell me, "Will you
go talk to Hannah about me?"
- I said, "Go tell her the
truth and say that you lied."
- You--no, no, no, no, no.
- Because you lied, dude.
- You never told me that.
- You lied--
- You said, "Go tell Hannah
that I'm here
for the right reasons."
- Because it's the truth,
and you are a liar.
That's what I was saying.
I was saying, "Please go admit
that you lied to her."
- Hey, I can understand
how you can feel
like you're being deceived.
But at the end of the day,
I told Hannah how I feel.
My feelings about you being
here for the right reasons
haven't changed.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[clears throat]
I didn't even wanna
talk to you--
or talk to Hannah about you.
You know, I told you--
- That's super, dude.
- I told you that I would
and I told her the truth.
- With you it's just
lie after lie,
manipulation after
manipulation.
I wish Hannah could see clearly
what--what's going on here.
- I--I can--I can understand
your frustration right now.
And I've admitted to Hannah
and I've admitted to you both
that I don't even
know you that well
and I don't have any business
saying whether you're here
for the right reasons or not.
So I don't--I don't--
- But--but you went ahead
and said that anyways.
I came here because I wanted
to fall in love
with an amazing woman,
and that's the only reason
why I came here, and, uh,
it's a shame that I had
to be involved with
a guy like you, uh,
and you had to, you know,
take me down.
I did my best
to be honest with her
and to be honest with everybody
in this whole process.
- I'm gonna be honest
with you, man.
I've been doing my complete
best to be completely open
and honest with her as well.
- Is that why you kneed me
in the head
while I was down on the ground?
- I was trying
to step over you, man.
Come on.
- You're so full of [bleep].
It's incredible.
You got it coming out
of your ears.
- Hi, fellas.
- Hi, Chris.
- You guys come here for a sec.
- Yep.
- Hey, Chris.
- Hello, Chris.
- Hey, guys.
Um...
This night's over.
Cocktail party's done.
We're going straight
to the Rose Ceremony.
[suspenseful music]
See you guys in there.
♪ ♪
- Damn, I'm pissed.
- Yeah. I called it.
- This is [bleep].
- What a piece of [bleep]
individual.
- Again, Luke P. made it
a night about himself.
Hannah took it upon herself
to cancel things early.
So we're in there
left with no time with her.
I'm very frustrated with
this whole Luke situation.
Everyone in the house is.
I believe it should be time
that Luke finally goes home.
- He stood up in front
of all of us and said, like,
"Okay, I'll tell her
the truth."
And then what did he do?
- I just cursed him out
earlier today.
It does not get through to him.
It sucks for Hannah to have to,
you know,
have all these emotions
going everywhere,
and then Luke P. only
making them worse.
I'm not intimidated
by him whatsoever.
If he gets a rose tonight
and he gets in my way,
I'll easily make sure
he doesn't do it again.
- Well, I know you guys don't
wanna hear anything
from me right now.
- No, we don't.
- We don't.
- We actually don't.
So save it, man.
[dramatic music]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- Are you cool with talking
for a minute or,
are you done with me?
- No, I--I don't wanna
talk to you anymore.
- Okay.
- It's upsetting, man.
- I agree with that.
- Because of the things that
transpired with both Lukes,
Hannah canceled
the cocktail party.
We just cut straight
to a Rose Ceremony.
She may respond by
letting them both go.
She might respond
by keeping Luke S.
She may respond by keeping
Luke P. and letting Luke S go.
There's no way of knowing
what she's gonna do.
♪ ♪
- Tonight was
a really rough night.
Luke P. has managed to make me
look really, really bad.
♪ ♪
That's just crazy how quickly
things changed
for the worse.
♪ ♪
- Um, tonight has been
a confusing night
to add to a hard week.
I...
Know every time going into this
that it's gonna be hard,
but it just continues to get
harder and harder.
But it's really important that
I continue to tap into
the strong woman that I am
and make decisions for myself
and follow my instincts
and my heart.
And tonight I'm gonna do that.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Um--um, may I talk to
you for a moment?
- Uh...
- Is it okay?
- Yeah, sure.
- Okay.
- I just wanted to let you know
that I am really sorry
if I've caused you
any, uh, pain.
It's just been hard for me
to have to defend my character
time and time again.
I would just urge you
to keep your eyes open
for, you know--I think you know
who I'm talking about.
[dramatic music]
- What do you guys think
they're talking about?
- Luke S. is fighting
for his livelihood as a man.
♪ ♪
- I'm not gonna tell you he's
a good guy or a bad guy.
♪ ♪
Just--just be wary.
Just keep your eyes open,
all right?
- Thanks.
- [whispers] All right, bye.
- [whispers] Thanks.
♪ ♪
- Oh.
There he goes.
- Think he just left.
- Just left.
- Good job, Luke P.
Hope that's what you wanted,
buddy.
♪ ♪
[footsteps approaching]
- Uh, Luke S.
just sent himself home.
I don't want anybody here
that doesn't want to be here.
So...
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Peter.
Peter, will you accept
this rose?
- Of course I will.
- Luke S. proved that he's not
the right one for Hannah.
I feel that he fell
to Luke P.'s game.
And now there is a possibility
Luke P. may go home tonight.
♪ ♪
- Connor.
Connor, will you accept
this rose?
- Of course.
- If I was Luke P.,
I would be very nervous.
He threw Luke S. under the bus
and I hope that Hannah
just chooses to send him home.
- Dylan.
♪ ♪
Dylan, will you accept
this rose?
- Of course.
- Dustin.
♪ ♪
Dustin, will you accept
this rose?
- Absolutely.
♪ ♪
- Mike.
Mike, will you accept
this rose?
- Absolutely.
♪ ♪
- Kevin.
Kevin, will you accept
this rose?
- Of course.
♪ ♪
- Devin.
Devin, will you accept
this rose?
- Of course.
- Grant.
♪ ♪
Grant, will you accept
this rose?
- Of course.
- Hannah, gentlemen,
this is the final rose tonight.
When you're ready.
♪ ♪
- [exhales]
- Luke P.
Luke, will you accept
this rose?
- Absolutely.
- Gentlemen, I'm sorry.
If you did not receive a rose,
take a moment.
Say your good-byes.
♪ ♪
- It was great to get
to know you.
Best of luck to you.
- Thank you so much.
The guys might not understand
and not get it,
but Luke P. is still here
because my...
heart wants him to be here.
My head doesn't always
want him to be here.
It makes it really
difficult to know
what's the best
decision to make.
Hey.
- It was great knowing you.
- We know we have
crazy chemistry.
But there were red flags,
and I honestly haven't had
the time to explore
our relationship
the way that I feel like it--
it needs to be explored.
Rhode Island has definitely
been eye-opening.
But, say we head overseas.
- All right.
- Yeah, amen.
- Hold on to your kilts.
all: Oh!
- We're going to Scotland,
lads!
all: Yay!
- Cheers to that.
- Are y'all excited?
'Cause I am.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, never been.
- I got a toast
for all you gentlemen.
But it's mostly for Hannah,
'cause we're all here
for Hannah.
To finding your forever
and having the time
of our lives
while on the hunt.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- [coughs]
- [laughs]
- Whoa, too strong
for you, Mike?
- [coughs]
I'm about to
fight for Hannah right now.
I see that there
are some people here
that think they have this
in the bag,
and little do they
know I'm coming.
♪ ♪
- Coming up tonight...
- I'm coming here
to win Hannah's heart,
and I don't like to lose.
- I need to show my queen
that I can be her king.
[overlapping shouting]
- Oh, my goodness.
Look at that!
- At the end of this,
I want to be engaged.
And for it to work,
you have to take the risk.
I like being with you.
- I like being with you.
- I know with conviction
that our connection is there.
It's real.
It's here to stay.
I can see myself getting down
on one knee
if I'm ever so lucky.
- The woman of my dreams is
slipping out of my fingers,
and I'm at the breaking point.
- This is about me caring
about Hannah,
not letting some little snake
slide his way into her heart
and her mind.
- I don't know.
I just felt like I needed
to tell you everything.
- I don't know what to do.
[dramatic music]
[sheep bleating]
[bagpipes playing]
♪ ♪
- This week we are
in Inverness, Scotland,
which is the capital
of the Highlands,
the jewel of Great Britain,
and the home
of the Loch Ness monster.
It's going to be a great
change of pace.
It's just cool to be somewhere
that has so much
culture and history behind it.
Mary, Queen of Scots
had to deal with a lot of men.
And she fought the battle
very, very hard.
But at the end of the day,
she was beheaded.
So I'm going to take the role
of Mary, Queen of Scots
except not end up beheaded.
♪ ♪
The guys are on their way here
and I am so excited
to see them.
[all shouting]
I want this week
to be a fresh start.
- Whoo!
- The past few weeks,
I've had a rocky time.
So I want the men to leave
the drama behind.
If they don't,
I'm just throwing them
to the Loch Ness Monster.
- Hey!
- Yeah!
- Look at this thing!
- Whoa!
This is a cool place.
- This is a castle?
- Welcome home.
We're staying here.
- Yeah, baby!
- Is this real life?
- Scotland!
- It's crazy.
We're here in Scotland.
We rolled up this morning
at the Achnagairn Estate,
which is a giant castle.
Never been to Scotland.
So cool to be here
and excited about it.
[all shouting]
- It's pretty sick.
It's awesome.
We walked through the doors
and it just--
the place oozes of history.
- Wow, look at the windows.
- Whoo!
- Can't believe
that we're here.
This is so cool.
We just traveled to Scotland.
We're staying in a castle.
Like, what is life right now?
- Whoa!
- Look at this view right now.
- Wow, this is crazy, man.
- This is crazy.
- This is just wild.
The only thing that could
make today better
is when I get that
one-on-one...
[laughs]
with Hannah.
I'm like,
bursting with bubbles
on the inside right now.
I'll show her
I'm her Braveheart.
all: Hannah!
[bicycle bell chimes]
- Whoo!
- Let's go.
So we're out roaming
the streets of Scotland.
But, like, I would so rather
be here with Hannah.
I feel like this is the perfect
place for couples.
[laughs]
- Let's get some drinks.
- You pick.
You surprise us, bartender.
- I'm definitely misunderstood
by the guys.
And if what they say about me
starts to creep into
what Hannah thinks about me,
you know, that's a line,
and that's when
I'm gonna step in
and I'm not gonna
allow that to happen.
Getting a one-on-one
is the most important thing
for me right now.
I'm in dire need of it.
So right now I'm really just
trying to continue
to prove Hannah my character.
all: Oh!
[all cheering]
- Welcome, welcome.
What a surprise.
- Did y'all not know
I was coming?
- No.
- Oh, okay, cool.
How are y'all doing, then?
- Wonderful.
- Um, okay.
I--I just have something
on my heart I just want to say.
It's nothin' bad.
I know usually, like,
you're, like, "Oh, [bleep].
Here she goes."
I keep preaching about, like,
being real,
and I've realized that
I haven't allowed myself
to completely open up
to you guys
as much as I would like to.
And there's relationships here
that, like,
are definitely built, like--
they're all building
but, like, at the end of this,
I want to be able
to be engaged.
So this week I had to refocus
and I've reset,
and I think we all should just
reset in this new country.
And that's why I'm just being
completely honest
and making sure that
from now on
I can open my heart.
So I just wanted to say that,
like, as soon as I saw y'all
so that, like, this week can
be, like, super fun
but we're all, like,
on the same page.
- Yes.
- Yes. Yeah.
- So cheers to focusing
on the real
and to focusing on
truly being able
to open our hearts to love.
Cheers.
- Cheers to that.
- Cheers.
[glasses clinking]
- So guess what?
all: What?
- Dates start now.
- Yo, why did my stomach--
- Ooh!
- Y'all, I felt butterflies
when she said, "Guess what."
- Yeah.
And I am ready to see a little
bit more of Scotland
and want to take somebody
with me to explore that.
So, uh, Mike, do you want
to go explore Scotland with me?
- I'd love to.
[laughter]
- Let's get out of here.
- Let's do it.
[laughs]
We're going on a one-on-one.
Whoo!
I'm so happy right now.
- Bye, y'all.
- Bye.
- I'm so excited to explore
Scotland with Hannah.
The other guys should be
on their toes
'cause Hannah's with me.
- Yay!
- How are you?
- [laughs]
- I'm so happy.
[laughs]
[tense music]
- I can promise you
she can tell
when she walked in
who was like,
"Oh, let me put on this
different persona
'cause Hannah's now here."
'Cause none of us were
expecting her
to walk in, right?
- Yeah.
- So I think she can--she can
sniff it out, dude.
- She wants you to be
organically yourself
to the absolute max.
- It's not necessarily who can
be the most themselves
but really that we can all be
ourselves the whole time.
And I don't know
about you guys.
I mean, I've--I know
we're all trying our best
to be ourselves here and I--
I mean,
I feel like I've been doing
my very best to do that but--
- I think that what can--
- Stop, stop.
- Go ahead.
- Luke, would you ever
say something
completely inaccurate
about someone
if you weren't
in this situation
like what you did with Luke S?
- I told Hannah that I thought
Luke wasn't here
for all the right reasons,
but before I said that,
I said, "Look, I don't really
have a place to--"
- But why did you say
that he wasn't here
for the right reason, though?
- So if you had to place
to say that then don't say it.
- Well, no, I understand that.
Now, I'm not talking bad
about Luke S.
- You--you literally--
you smeared him.
You smeared him.
You're a liar.
- No, I'm not.
- The reason that
we can't trust you--
- You weren't there.
You don't know
what you speak of.
They can believe and think
what they want about me.
I really don't care.
My only concern is my
relationship with Hannah.
But I'm looking at all these
guys and I'm just like,
"Dude, you are so
what's not for Hannah,
it makes me want to gag."
Look, I have no business saying
anything about Luke S.
Can you take everything
I've said about him
and, like, just put that
to the side?
'Cause I haven't--I don't
even know the guy.
- Here's my--hey, hold on,
hold on, hold on.
Don't take what people
are saying to you
and put it in your own words
to Hannah.
Especially me.
'Cause you don't wanna do that.
I promise.
Just don't cross
the line anymore.
He still can't get
his story straight.
Everything is twisted.
Every single thing that he says
is changed and switched around.
This isn't about me trying
to throw him under the bus.
This is about me caring
about Hannah
and not letting the Luke Ness
Monster slide his way
into her heart and her mind
and poison her.
[folk music]
- I'm so happy.
I'm so happy.
- I'm so happy
that you're happy.
- [laughs]
[both laughing]
- I'm so excited to explore
the city today.
Doing all the Scottish things.
I love it.
You look so cute!
Mike couldn't stop smiling
when I called him
to come with me.
[laughs]
Books, maps, and prints.
Let's try it.
[gasps]
- Oh, wow.
- Oh, it smells--
[sniffs]
I love that fresh book smell.
- [laughs]
- Goose eggs.
- Did you have eggs
this morning or no?
- I did.
I don't know why I put it up
to my ear, though.
I have no idea why
I just did that.
- [laughs]
- Mike's fun and funny
and very handsome.
- "O my love's like a red,
red rose
"that's newly sprung in June.
O my love's like a melody
that's sweetly played in tune."
[laughs]
- That was great.
I love that he's adventurous.
I know the man that
I want to be with
is going to want
to explore the world,
and I want to be
a part of that.
Oh.
We're going in here.
I have the biggest sweet tooth
of anybody.
[gasps]
Oh, my goodness.
My eyes are feasting.
What are some good things
I can try?
- Black Death?
- Black Death.
both: If you dare.
- I'll try it.
- [coughs]
[quirky music]
- [laughs]
- Pretty good.
[laughs]
I see why you need to
tell us that prior to.
- Mmm.
Oh.
- [laughs]
- Mike and I conquered
the Black Death.
[both laughing]
Mike makes me feel comfortable
enough to just be myself,
and I love that.
- This is a classic
Highland whiskey.
- Do you know what
Southern women are?
- Southern women?
- Whiskey in a teacup.
- [laughs]
- We're strong in the inside
but ornate on the outside.
- And is that your cup of tea?
- Absolutely.
- Oh, yeah.
To me looking deeper
in your eyes
and getting to know you more.
- Cheers.
- Cheers, guys.
- Mike and I tried whiskey.
Whoo!
- This is a more smoky one.
- A lot of them.
I got a little bit more swaggy
in my step now.
Hey.
[both laughing]
- Hannah's amazing.
She's silly and she's genuine.
I love it, love it, love it.
You smile so much.
- Do I?
- Yeah, you do.
- Oh, good.
- I love life right now.
I'm feeling feelings today.
Honestly, 100%.
It's a perfect day to fall
in love here in Scotland
with Hannah by my side.
This is our first date
in Scotland
and many more to come.
- Our first--
[laughs]
- You ever tried haggis?
It's the local Scottish food.
- Get us some haggis.
- Give them some haggis.
- Pronto.
Oh, God, now he's scaring me.
Is this like--
- Is this Loch Ness Monster?
- Part of
the Loch Ness Monster.
- It's good.
How do you like it?
- I like Haggis.
- I like it.
- You like haggis?
- What is it?
- It's the intestines of sheep
cooked in, uh,
skin of the belly of the sheep.
It's not good.
I--I don't--
I don't eat it.
- You don't eat haggis?
- No, no.
No, no, no.
I'm English.
I don't eat this.
- Oh, my God!
[laughs]
- No, no, no.
[quirky music]
♪ ♪
- Luke's had the chance
every single week
to kind of put himself
in a better light.
With a new week starting
in a new country
for God sakes, this week,
he still twisted your words.
Man, that's--it triggered
everyone because
I think everyone had
the same attitude of,
"Okay, let's just
move on from it."
But then again he proves
today that you can't trust
anything that he says.
- I don't know if he just
doesn't think
or if he's methodical
about how he answers things.
It's confusing.
- We do need to watch
our words around him.
Luke needs to watch his step.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause he could cross up
the wrong person here.
- Exactly.
As long as he's here,
there's going
to be something going on.
Simple as that.
♪ ♪
- I'm really glad
you're here today.
- No, I'm glad I'm here today.
- I, um--I feel like a lot
of the last few conversations
we've had haven't
been about us
and it's been about
different things,
so I really wanted today
for us to just focus on
our relationship.
So I'm glad we got that.
- I ain't worried about nobody.
- Yeah.
- My time is with you.
And my time with you,
I'm loving that you
can be silly.
- No, but I think
it's really important.
Like, yes, there has to be
serious conversations
but if you don't make each
other laugh and, like,
when those bad times come,
like, there--
- There won't be nothing
to get through it.
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm with you.
Like, I've been...
I've been through it.
Believe me.
- Yeah.
- I wanted--I wanted to smile.
That's why I said my time
with you just being silly
is everything for me.
My--I can't stop smiling.
I just want to be around you.
More and more and more
and more and more.
That sounds kind of weird,
right?
- No.
- Okay.
[laughs]
- Cheers.
- Okay.
[laughs]
Today's going great.
Our bond is very unique
and genuine.
- Let's get out of here.
- Ready, my darling?
- It takes me longer
than an average person
to fall in love,
but our connection is there.
It's as real as I thought it
was during the group dates.
And now I know with
conviction it's there.
It's real.
It's here to stay.
- Oh, my God.
Look how pretty it is.
[uplifting music]
♪ ♪
- Kissing Hannah right here
in Inverness, Scotland
is by far the most magical,
miraculous moment in my life.
♪ ♪
And I can't wait
for so much more.
[both laughing]
[dramatic music]
- Yeah, I'm actually nervous
for the first time.
- Don't be nervous.
- Hannah and I had some
magical moments today.
Laughter, smiles,
just genuine happiness.
But tonight I'm so nervous.
Last time I was this nervous
was December 25th, 2013.
That's when I told my ex
that I loved her.
We broke up in 2015.
She really broke my heart.
And so I am terrified
to fall in love again.
Oh, my God.
- It smells good.
- With Hannah I can see us
creating a life together.
I can 100% see myself falling
in love with Hannah.
Tonight I wanna tell her
exactly how I feel.
Um, so I had
a great time today.
When we went
to the candy store
and I saw your face...
- [laughs]
- On that sour thing,
you were just--
- [laughs]
- And I was--I thought
that was pretty awesome.
- And we can't forget
about the whiskey.
- Oh, no, I didn't forget
- I had a great time.
- You had a good time--
- I felt comfortable
to have a good time.
- I appreciate that.
Same.
- Mm-hmm.
- Definitely so.
It's awesome
I'm...blessed
and privileged and happy
and I want to know a little
about you and your past
and how you ended up here.
- Um, the past two years,
I would say,
has been so eye-opening for me.
I realize that, like,
I've been living my life
from man to man
and adapting myself
to those relationships because
I didn't love myself enough.
And then there were nights
where I would just cry
and feel completely broken.
I became the person I was
supposed to be through that.
- Definitely so.
I appreciate you
telling me that.
I'm not one to open up
to everybody,
just because I hold the things
in my life near and dear.
- Mm-hmm.
- And...
I'm even more like that
with things of love
and things like that.
Um, it's really,
really hard for me.
I'm sounding like a little kid.
- Just talk.
You're fine.
- This is just not easy for me.
I'm not this--
I don't do this.
I'm sorry.
[laughs]
You make me nervous
and I'm not one to get nervous.
- Why do I make you nervous?
- You're making me nervous
because I...
do not want to
get my heart broken again.
- Look, this thing is obv--
I'm just gonna say, like,
this, it's a very scary way
to find love.
But for it to ever work,
you have to take the risk.
- That's facts.
[laughs]
- Do you need to a break?
- No, I'm good.
I just need a drink.
[laughs]
This is the first time
this entire journey
I've been this nervous.
I haven't been in love
for almost half a decade.
And now that I'm around her
and I'm growing so many
intense feelings for her,
I am terrified.
[knocking on door]
- Date card, huh?
- I got it, fellas.
- Hey.
- All right.
- I frankly hope that
it's a group date
and my name's not on it because
that means that my name's
on the next one-on-one card.
I know we have
a strong relationship
and, uh, we just gotta
keep building.
[quirky music]
- Devin,
Tyler,
Jed,
Dylan, Grant,
Connor,
Dustin,
Peter,
Kevin.
♪ ♪
Garrett.
"Love is a battlefield.
Hannah."
- So whose name
didn't make the list?
You.
- Yeah, I mean,
I'm definitely stoked.
I can't wait to not have
any distractions
and just to focus
on my relationship with her.
I feel like just to be honest
I'm at the breaking point
where, you know, after this
I'm gonna really know
if I really want
to be here still.
[tense music]
And I hope that I really
find clarity
in how I feel about her.
- Luke literally went
from the first group date
saying he was falling in love.
Now he's saying he's just
excited to see
where his relationship
is with Hannah.
I think Hannah's really smart,
so I think it's gonna give her
just a lot of clarity.
- If you find that you're not
here and you're not interested
in Hannah in that way,
then be honest about it.
You have gone kinda back
and forth in regard
to, like, whether or not
you are or you aren't.
Just be honest.
I want to give Luke P.
the benefit of the doubt.
But honestly at this point,
I just feel like he's
a big-ass douche canoe.
- So I told you I was
in the military.
- Mm-hmm.
- And--
See, now, help me now,
help me now, help me now.
- You're good, you're good.
- I think I did tell you
I'm, like,
kind of a hopeless romantic
in a sense.
Like I thought I'd only tell
one woman I love her.
And I meant it then.
And when we broke up,
it took me a long time
to get over it.
I mean, years.
And so just know
that I'm 31 years old.
I've learned a lot of things
in my life.
I've been around the world,
and I truly know who I am
and I know what I want.
I'm really ready.
I'm really, really ready.
I can see myself getting
down on one knee
in a few weeks...
if I'm ever so lucky.
- Well, thank you.
[laughs]
♪ ♪
Well...
[laughs]
- Ah, I really
love those things.
[both laughing]
- Today you took giant steps
to be open and vulnerable
with me
and allowed me to see
what could be.
And that makes me really
excited to continue to grow
and know you more.
So, Mike...
- Hannah.
- Will you accept this rose?
- Of course I will.
- [laughs]
- Does it fit on there?
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
♪ ♪
- What I feel Hannah's telling
me by giving me the rose
is that she feels that she
can fall in love with me.
And I very may well be
falling in love with her.
- Here's to so much more.
- Let's go.
- Today was fun and adventurous
and tonight we had
the best conversation.
He showed me more of
a vulnerable side emotionally.
- Let's party.
- Scottish party!
[fiddling music]
This is amazing!
♪ ♪
Mike is confident, and he's
also been through a lot
and learned a lot,
so he's very wise
in love and life.
♪ ♪
Mike has a lot of layers
to him
and those layers are what make
him so attractive to me
and make our relationship
a real relationship.
I could see a future with him
if it keeps going
the way it is.
♪ ♪
- Coming up...
[both shouting]
- I'm here to show her
that I'm a fighter.
I'll never quit.
- Focus.
- [shouting]
- These men need to work
on their aim.
[all shouting]
Bow down to your queen.
- And then...
- I can't ignore the fact
that today went so great
and Luke P.
wasn't on this group date.
It's just, like, frustrating.
This doesn't make sense
why the guys don't like you.
Like, I just don't understand.
I just want you to speak.
- Well, I don't know what
you want me to explain.
- [groans]
[geese honking]
- Boys, let's go.
[overlapping chatter]
- Hello.
- Oh, my God.
- Hannah!
- She looks so cute.
She has her little kilt on
and a little, like, snow cap.
Literally, like, our princess
is waiting there for us.
- Loving the skirt.
- It's my tartan.
- I'm very excited.
I mean, we're at--we're at this
pretty insane castle
and Luke P.'s not
on our group date today.
Not gonna be any drama,
I'm hoping.
Now we can really just focus
on Hannah.
- Welcome to the Highlands.
[both shouting]
- Oh, my God.
- Oh.
- Oh, man.
- Guys, this is Charlie.
He is a world-renowned
battle reenactor.
- Are you ready for this?
- Sure.
- Absolutely.
- Are you up for this?
all: Yes.
- We're gonna start
the competition now.
I wanna see your war face!
- A war face!
- Yeah!
[both screaming]
- We are participating
in old Scottish games.
You know, you gotta
impress Hannah.
[both screaming]
- I'm here to show her
that I'm a fighter.
I'll never quit.
I got that fire in me.
And let the games begin, baby.
- Ah!
- Ooh.
- Chop some wood.
- [shouts]
- These men need to work
on their aim.
- Hah!
- Ah!
- Ooh.
Show the lady you mean it.
- [shouts]
- Ooh!
- That sucked.
- My turn.
- Let 'er rip.
[all shouting]
- Yeah!
- Damn!
Oh!
Bow down to your Queen.
Bow!
- Hannah was the only one
who stuck her axe in the wood.
It was pretty impressive.
- Right, gentlemen,
next up is the yolk race.
- Go!
- Don't drop the milk.
- Oh!
- Oh, no.
- Well, y'all both
spilled the milk.
I'm looking for strength.
Not just physical strength,
but strength of heart.
- No spilled milk.
- I'm looking
for a brave heart.
- So next one up is
a Scottish backhoe wrestling.
- It's gonna get dirty.
- [laughs]
- Oh!
- That will do.
- I hope with Hannah being
as perceptive as she is
that she sees finally a group
date without Luke P.
and she's able to have
some fun.
- Get him!
- Oh!
Oh!
- Get him!
- Luke P. would really try
to make it a day about him
rather than Hannah.
- That was fun.
- I am concerned deeply
with what you intend
to tell Hannah tomorrow.
Multiple times
you've questioned
if you wanna be here.
- I've never questioned that.
- That's crazy, uh,
because I know last night
you questioned wanting
to be here again and--
- Last night?
- Last night you questioned
wanting to be here again.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, what--
when--
what are you talking about?
- You have selective memory,
man.
'Cause you have said it.
- Dude, what exactly
do you think I said?
Because my feelings for her
from the first date
to now has not changed
one single bit.
- [groans]
- All right.
- Luke P., he hates the fact
that I'm calling him out
on all his [bleep].
Tomorrow he gets a one-on-one
with Hannah
and he's not sure if
he wants to be here.
That's his first thought?
He's giving my girl Hannah
mixed emotions.
But she sees his [bleep].
She loves his exterior,
but she's reading through
that exterior and getting
to the interior
and she's gonna see that he's
the Loch Ness Monster.
"The monster is all too apt
to inspire disbelief
"or faith that borders
on mania.
"There is no doubt something
unexplained exists
"underneath the surface.
"This monster
is cagey and elusive
to all but those with
the keenest eye."
Crazy.
Hannah's gonna see it.
She's gonna realize
the real Luke P.
He's a Luke Ness Monster.
♪ ♪
[all shouting]
- It is cold!
- Oh, man.
- Going all the way down.
- It's not normally that small.
- Don't lie.
- We just put on kilts
and, uh, yeah.
We're feeling a little cold,
a little breezy.
- Whoo!
- But it'll be a good time.
- We're about to do
the highland games.
We're about to get real now.
Today little Braveheart's
coming.
- I'm ready to go.
I'm ready for war.
[shouts]
[cheers and applause]
[bagpipes playing]
- It's time for
the Highland games.
[all shouting]
Charge!
May the best man win.
[all shouting]
[suspenseful music]
How do y'all feel
in your kilts, huh?
- Welcome to the first
"Bachelorette" Highland games.
[cheers and applause]
Okay, guys, first up
is the axe throwing.
- Let's go!
♪ ♪
all: Aww.
- Eh, they did what they could.
all: Oh!
- They all tried.
- Oh!
- Some just need to try harder.
all: Oh!
- God, we suck.
- I'm coming here to win
Hannah's heart today.
And I don't like to lose.
I don't lose.
- Last but not least, Tyler.
[cheering]
[all shouting]
- Tyler was really impressive
with the axe throwing.
And Tyler is hot.
- Now the guys are gonna do
a thing called the yolk race.
- Hannah's, like,
an amazing woman.
I need to show my queen
that I could be her king.
- One, two, three.
- Three!
Whoo!
- Obviously it was, you know,
a bunch of competition.
I just--I want to show
her who I am.
- Peter won.
- Hey!
- Whoo!
Yeah, Peter!
Today Peter was really good.
- Next up is Jed and Kevin!
- All the guys were
so amazing.
Come on, guys!
They all had fun but also
when it was competition time,
they showed that.
[cheering]
[laughter]
- Yeah!
- Jed poured that milk
over him, and it was hot.
- Final event for today is the
Scottish backhoe wrestling.
[all oohing]
- We don't have [bleep]
underwear on.
- Dylan and Devin,
first up.
- I'm not wearing
any underwear,
so definitely concerned
about showing my butt.
- Let's go, boys.
- Whoo!
[all oohing]
- Ready, go.
[suspenseful music]
[overlapping yelling]
- Guys, my eyes!
- You know, my mom's probably
gonna be upset
that all those people
saw my butt,
but, uh, oh well.
- Whoa!
[all screaming]
- I saw your nuts, Connor.
- No, you didn't.
- Yes, I did.
- I saw all of the bagpipes.
My eyes!
But at the same time it's not
the size of your bagpipe.
It's how you play it.
- [shouting]
- We're still neck and neck
going for Hannah's heart.
- [screaming]
War is my duty, but I'm also
here for Hannah's booty.
And I have a little something
up my sleeve.
I would love to battle
anyone here,
but I kinda wanna be pinned
by the queen.
- [laughs]
Okay.
- Okay?
- Come on, Hannah!
- All right.
- Okay, ready?
One, two--
[laughs]
[cheering]
[applause]
- Boo! Good job.
Boo!
- There can only be one winner.
Jed.
[cheering]
♪ ♪
- You never wanna see someone
kissing your lady, you know?
And that just--tonight's gonna
be about me and Hannah.
- Whoo!
- It was a little bit
of a dagger.
- Boo.
- But maybe I didn't win
on the field today,
but I'm definitely gonna make
an impression tonight
that she won't forget.
- Let's get going!
- Let's go!
- Charge!
Whoo!
[bell tolling]
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- Welcome to my castle.
- Wow.
- Thank you.
- Well, this is--
- Whoa.
- Isn't this beautiful?
- Look!
Be careful or that will be you,
beheaded.
Did y'all have fun today?
- Oh, yeah.
- A blast.
- Cheers to opening up
our hearts to each other
and finding strength
of the heart
and continuing to develop
our relationship.
Cheers.
together: Cheers.
[glasses clink]
- Tonight is a good night
to really focus
on the other
individual relationships here
without Luke being
the focus of the evening.
This is really about
moving our relationships
in the right direction.
I'm really looking forward
to being in the moment
with these guys
and not worrying about
any drama going on elsewhere.
- I missed the [bleep]
out of you.
- Really?
- Uh-huh.
- I missed you too.
Today you won.
- I did. I won.
- So you were basically
like the winner of the land.
- This my land now?
- It actually is.
- No.
- Yes.
You have a land deed.
It's basically
just a square foot.
- That is so--
- So you're a lord.
- You're Lord Jed.
- Oh, my God.
- And I'm Lady Hannah.
- Lady Hannah.
- Lady Hannah...
- And Lord Jed.
- Bring us grapes.
- Grapes.
- [laughs]
Grapes.
- Hell, that's awesome.
I like the way that sounds.
- [laughs]
[romantic music]
♪ ♪
- Does this dress allow this?
- Who cares?
♪ ♪
I like being with you.
- I like being with you.
♪ ♪
[quirky music]
- Walked up the stairs,
and Hannah had, like, Jed
pinned down, like, attacking
the [bleep] out of him.
♪ ♪
I'm just sitting there
watching this
for, like, 15, 20 seconds.
I'm like, "Oh, my [bleep]."
I mean, me and Hannah
have not kissed yet.
Of course I wished
that was me.
♪ ♪
- You did see Hannah?
- I did, yeah.
- How was it?
- It was good.
It was really good.
- Yeah, I accidentally
saw it as well.
It was...
I know it was great.
[laughter]
- How long were you there?
- It's like one of those things
that you see
and you can't turn away from.
- I'm sorry, but I'm not sorry.
[laughter]
- Okay, yeah.
- All right, we made contact.
That's good.
- I made contact.
- Should put this right here.
And clear these out.
That was not smooth.
- [laughs]
- Let me do that one more time.
That was not smooth
whatsoever.
- What's gonna happen?
- I don't know.
I just...wanted
to get you onto...
this...
- [laughs]
- Oh, my God.
This--I have never
done this before.
- Me either.
[sultry music]
♪ ♪
- Making out with Hannah
on this pool table,
it feels so...
just, like, hot and sexy,
just, like, all that stuff
that I want
and just so right,
and I just--I don't
want this to end.
♪ ♪
[clock ticking]
[knocking]
[dramatic music]
- Mike doesn't say anything
to me, and walks out.
[scoffs]
Really, man?
Like, it's like that?
But, you know,
it's like that between us.
They can believe and think
what they want about me.
I really don't care.
I care what Hannah
thinks about me.
♪ ♪
[laughs]
"Luke,
let's figure things out
one way or another.
Hannah."
One way or another, Luke,
we're gonna get through this.
I can't wait to have
alone time with my girl.
I'm ready.
- You pushing me motivates me,
and I want you to know
I'm officially ready
to take the next step.
[gentle music]
- Today was just more
than I could have expected.
- I'm gonna fight for you.
Like, I want, you know,
us to be able to grow
our relationship, and I really,
really do like you a lot.
- All the guys
were so amazing...
[speaking Gaelic]
- Okay, that means in Gaelic,
"It takes time
to build a castle."
Just really stepped it up,
had fun.
Workin' that kilt.
- I saw you creepin',
so I brought it back in case
you wanted to take another
peek, you know what I mean?
- It's just made me
really hopeful
about what the future
of this can be.
- But today was a blast.
- You're the only one
that could wax the axe.
- Could what?
- Wax the axe.
- I thought you said,
"You're the only one
that could wax my ass."
I was like, all right.
Well, I'm glad
we're that close.
- I have something.
Come here.
- For me?
- Yeah.
- All right.
[gentle music]
Huh.
- What?
♪ ♪
Ooh.
- [laughs]
- Oh.
♪ ♪
- Well, I can get used to that.
I'm gonna wear my kilt
a lot more.
I feel that me and Hannah
have really had
a strong connection,
and I feel that, you know,
just in the way we kissed,
the way we talk to each other.
I feel that we made such a
great, you know, stride today
and more leaps and bounds
in our relationship,
and it was an amazing feeling.
I think that Group Date Rose
is mine.
- Today, like, has been
so great for me,
and I think we all needed
some fresh Scottish air.
[laughs]
But I wanna give this rose
to someone who impresses me,
and we really took a new lease
on our love today,
so, Jed, will you
accept this rose?
- I will.
- [laughs]
All day, you've been great.
- Lady Hannah.
- [laughs]
Today was perfect for me.
I was seeing hope
and feeling loved.
I felt no sense of drama.
Bye, guys.
It would be ignorant of me
to ignore the fact
that today went so great
and Luke P. wasn't
on this group date.
So it's a really
big day tomorrow.
I need to get to bottom of
concerns I have with Luke P.
and if we can
get past all this.
I'm looking for answers.
- Coming up...
- Oh, my goodness.
You look fantastic.
I don't see this day going
any other way than phenomenal.
- It's just, like, frustrating,
'cause I'm, like,
trying everything.
- I don't want--I don't know
what you want me to explain.
- God, don't say that.
Like, I don't know what to do.
[birds chirping]
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- I think Hannah had, like,
the best day yesterday.
She just had so much fun.
She was so much fun to be with,
you know,
in our group date setting,
and she even said it.
You know,
she talked about, like,
how that was such a fun time.
It was so refreshing.
- I think it was
a contrast for her
to see that this
group date went well--
Luke P. wasn't there.
- Yeah.
- It's not a secret.
None of us care for Luke P.
He's showing Hannah one face,
and then he's showing us
a completely different side.
The guy is just a liar, man.
I feel that Hannah will catch
up to all of Luke's lies
and realize this
is a [bleep] sandwich.
Throw it away.
[door creaks]
- [clears throat]
- Yo, yo.
- What's happening, guys?
- What's up?
- How y'all doing?
[murmured replies]
- Heard you guys
were wearing kilts out there
and wrestling in them.
[laughs]
- You got a big day.
Are you stoked?
- Definitely, I'm excited
exploring a little bit
of Scotland, so...
With Hannah.
- Listen, be a man and keep
our names out your mouth,
just flat out.
- I plan on it.
- Do you?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- All right, guys.
I'm gonna get going.
You guys enjoy yourselves
at the house.
- All right, have a good one.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- I'm really excited
to see Luke,
but I think I've had
a lot of anxiety about today.
There's no denying
the connection that we have.
There's also no denying
that there are red flags
everywhere.
He is very much disliked by
every other man in the house.
He doesn't always
express his emotions.
He seems like
he's trying to be perfect,
and it comes off really fake.
Today I hope we can kinda
get down to the bottom
of some of these
crucial questions
for our relationship.
Either today
is the first one-on-one
with my future husband,
or it's the first and last
one-on-one date with Luke.
Hey.
- How are you?
- Hey.
- [laughs]
- You look fantastic.
Like, for sure.
How are you doing?
- I'm good.
- Are you?
- I'm glad you're here.
- Thank you--me too.
[laughs]
Oh, I'm so excited.
- Oh!
- This is so beautiful.
Look at the ocean.
- I know.
- I really didn't expect
Scotland would be this pretty.
- I know, it's gorgeous,
though.
- It's beautiful.
But look at these flowers.
I saw these, and I was like,
"I would love just
to hold Hannah's hand and walk
through these with her."
- Well, look.
- [laughs]
- That's what we're doing.
- I love it.
I cannot wait to spend the day
with Hannah.
I'm just ready to be me.
All this one-on-one is gonna do
is continue to give me clarity
about the future with Hannah.
This is already going
a lot better than I thought.
[both laugh]
- Yeah.
- Oh, my goodness!
Look--look at that!
What?
- Yep, that's where
we're going.
- No way.
I know Hannah's really excited
to spend alone time with me,
so I don't see
this day going
any other way
than phenomenal.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
How are you doing?
- Are you?
- Are you good?
- You look good.
[laughs]
- Thank you.
You don't look bad yourself.
- Were you shocked when you--
like, did you know you were--
this was gonna
happen this week?
- No, not at all.
I felt like it made
a little bit of sense, though,
for sure...
- Mm-hmm.
- Especially after the last
few weeks, which, between us,
I don't think have gone
anything like I would have
liked, but...
- Yeah.
- We're getting
through it, though.
Uh, to be honest,
I didn't want to talk about
the last few weeks at all
the whole time I was with you,
but I just wanted to make sure
that we're on the same page.
Is there anything that
you wanted to talk about?
- Yeah, um...
We talked about the things
that I was concerned about,
you know, the week before.
- I remember.
[both laugh]
- And then last week,
all the guys saying
how they felt about you
just, like, really...
bothered me because
I just don't get it,
like, why...the guys
don't like you.
Like, I just...
don't understand.
- Let me just begin
with last week.
I did a lot of thinking,
just trying to put myself
in their shoes.
I know now the root of it,
and it comes down
to that conversation we had
when you asked me,
"What's going on
between you and Luke S.?"
Like, I could have handled
that whole sideline situation
a whole lot better.
I admit that.
I--I screwed up.
But, you know, when you asked
me what I think of Luke S.,
I don't know,
I just felt like
I needed to tell you
everything.
'Cause I have had thoughts,
multiple times,
of him just truly not being
here for the right reasons.
The guys kinda...
came at me harsh about
they thought I was
trying to get a pity rose
and resolve
the whole rugby thing.
That was never my intentions.
I knew from
the beginning of that day,
I was never worried
about our relationship,
and I don't know, I just think
in the heat of the moment,
I just wanted to share with you
truly how I felt.
I don't--I didn't
know him that well,
I had no business saying it,
but I felt that way,
and I felt like you
needed to know that.
- That--yeah.
And, I mean...
It's not really
the Luke S. thing.
Like, it's...
- Other things?
- It's other things that I
think that you've said or done.
I mean, it just
doesn't make sense
why every single guy
had something to say.
- I, like--I've asked guys
like Mike, for instance.
I was like, "Can you give me
examples of things
"that I've done that have
questioned my character
besides this whole
rugby day altogether?"
People put words in my mouth
and twisted a lot
of what I said.
It's something that has been
happening a lot
around the guys.
Like, Dylan and Devin were
a little frustrated with me
'cause now I say anything,
and they blow it
way out of proportion.
Anything that I do,
they're just trying to amplify
it in a negative way,
and it's a very tough position
I'm in right now.
And it's not easy,
but I'm never gonna quit.
- Yeah.
Um...one thing that, like--
that I'm looking for and that,
like, bothers me, I want a man
that people are drawn to.
Like, what's inside
is appealing.
People are not being
drawn to you here.
- It's really not adding up.
But everyone I've ever met,
every place,
every school I've ever been,
anywhere I've ever been
in my whole life,
everyone loves me.
- God, don't--
That's so--okay.
- I know, I hate saying it,
but it's the truth.
And, like, I hate
talking about myself,
but I don't ever want
to tell you things about me.
- I know, but don't say things
like, "People love me."
That makes me so mad.
- Okay, it's not me.
It's just--
- I know,
but that's something--
- The person that I've--
- I understand that,
and I can see that,
but I don't like--
That's where I think that
there are issues with the guys.
You know, like,
that sounded boastful.
Do you understand
how that sounds?
- Yes, it sounds terrible.
I know.
- I don't know.
It's just, like, frustrating
because I'm, like,
trying everything to, like--
- I don't know
what you want me to say.
- I don't want you
to say anything from--
like,
I just want you to speak.
- I don't know what
you want me to explain.
I just want
to give you clarity.
I want you to get
to know who I am,
so I'm ready to go do whatever
we have planned for the day
and you just
enjoy the day with me.
- I know. It's just...
[sighs]
I don't want to know,
like, what happened.
I want to know, like,
how it affects you,
like your heart and me.
Does that make sense?
- Yes.
- Like, how does
it make you feel?
Like, how is all this
with our relationship,
with you as a person, like...
- I've just been
continuing to be myself
and be very respectful
of everybody else,
even throughout
being disrespected
throughout conversations,
so how does it make me feel?
[small laugh]
- Feelings.
- Yeah, I think--
I mean, I don't think.
I know that it's not right.
A lot of how they're treating
me is totally not right,
but it's not affecting me,
because I know I'm here for you
and I'm not ever gonna
lose sight of that
and I want to give you clarity.
That's all I want for you.
- Yeah.
- Did I answer that
well enough?
- No.
I mean, you did,
you did answer it,
but, like...
[dramatic music]
Do you wanna know
how it makes me feel?
Like...ugh.
Will you just give me a second?
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
- There's no feelings behind
the things that he's saying.
Like...
I don't know
where his heart's at.
I know he says
he's here for me,
but I don't really know.
♪ ♪
Can you not express
your emotions?
'Cause, like, I need more.
♪ ♪
[solemn music]
- So, I knew coming
into this one-on-one date
that I had some stuff
to clear up with Hannah.
So right now,
we're working through things,
we're talking through things,
and it's good.
It's healthy
for our relationship
because all I want for us is
to be able to move past this,
be on the same page,
and I wanna really
give her clarity.
- Like, I don't know
what to do.
There's something there.
I just, like, don't...
know how to get out of this.
And I don't wanna
give up on it,
and I wanna get past it.
- It takes time.
It just takes time.
- Like, he has
to have emotions.
Like, it's obvious
he has emotions,
but, like, speak the emotions,
I guess, right?
- Yeah.
- Is that what's missing?
Like, I feel like
that's what's missing, and I--
[sighs]
Can somebody talk to him
about what it means
when I say,
"How do you feel?"
- You have to talk
to him about--
- You need to talk to him
about that.
[dramatic music]
- All right.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
- Hey.
It hurts me.
This is--this is--
[sighs]
This is not easy for me
in any way right now,
and I know, if anything,
it's harder on you.
And I'm gonna do
everything in my power
to make things clear for you
and to make things right.
I want you to know that.
- You can't just,
like, keep saying that.
Like, I don't wanna hear that.
Like, I'm really trying...
to understand you,
but the only way
that I'm gonna understand you
is for you to, like,
not just talk about
what happened or,
like, how you're gonna
keep trying because you know
that it hurts me, like...
I don't know,
just, like...
I need more.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
I don't know--we're not gonna
get there, like, right now.
Let's go look at this castle.
- Enough said.
You wanna get your coat?
- Yeah, I do.
♪ ♪
- There you go.
- Okay, come on, let's go.
- Let's do it.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
Is there anything
that I left out
that you want me
to explain to you?
- I just feel like you say
things that you know
that I'm gonna like and that,
like, are important to me,
and I just wanna, like, talk to
you about, like, normal stuff.
Like, crap happens,
and I just wanna know, like,
do you like macaroni and cheese
or spaghetti more?
Like, I just want to know,
like, the real stuff,
and it's just frustrating
'cause I just feel like it's--
you're just, like, talking
in ways that just sound good.
- Listen, listen, listen,
I'm sorry.
I just don't want you
to ever think
I'm trying to say
what you want me to say.
I'm never gonna do that
through this whole process,
and I'm sorry if you feel like
I did try to do that.
I'm never gonna do that,
I promise, okay?
- I don't know.
- Do you wanna
keep going for a walk?
- No, I just wanna stand
right here when I get mad
and talk for a second.
Don't just--I don't know.
I don't know.
I just, like,
need the real, and--and...
Real isn't...
I don't know.
I don't know what I want.
Let's go look at this castle.
- All right.
[contemplative music]
- I'm very conflicted.
I really like Luke P.,
and I hate admitting it
'cause I want to not like him.
I want to be able
to send him home
just like I've sent home
every other guy
that's pissed me off,
but I can't.
- Wow, this is really cool.
- What if I let go of Luke
but he's who
I'm supposed to be with?
I have no idea
what I'm gonna do tonight.
I don't know
how much more I can do
to see tonight turned around.
I can't keep
making excuses for him
when I'm not doing that
with anybody else.
[dramatic music]
[sighs]
♪ ♪
- Hey, hey.
- Hey.
- I like this fur coat.
- Thank you.
- Oh.
- Today was terrible.
I just feel like Luke
didn't really open up.
It's just, he said
the same things
that I've heard
over and over again.
- Which one's you?
- He doesn't really say
exactly what he's doing wrong.
He, like,
gives excuses for it.
I've told him
what I need from him
and what I need
from a relationship,
and so tonight, it's very
important for me to see him
step maybe
out of his comfort zone
to fight for the relationship.
I was really
hopeful for today...
- Mm-hmm.
- And, um, really wanted to,
like, focus on our connection
and our relationship, and,
honestly, as much as I wanted
to do that, I couldn't
because I wasn't feeling
like I was getting met
where I needed to be.
- Mm-hmm.
- And...I mean,
I feel like it was obvious that
the day didn't go very well.
- You know, I won't lie.
Just being honest.
I felt like today was gonna go
a lot better than it did,
and I haven't been worried
about where I'm at
with my relationship with you,
but there has been moments
where I feel like--
um, just to be honest with you,
I feel like I've been
kind of like
on thin ice with you.
And, like, do you know
what I'm trying to say?
- Yeah, I know--I know
what you're trying to say,
and, like...
Um...
I understand
where that's coming from
about feeling like
you're on thin ice
because, yeah, you are.
I--like, I--
Hearing you say, like,
you don't...you know,
have any worries
about our relationship--
I def--I--I do.
Like...
- Right.
- There's, like,
a great man inside,
but, like, there's these walls
that have been put up
that, like, I can't break
through because
you're trying to protect
what you want people to see
instead of just, like, saying,
"It wasn't my intention.
"I'm a great guy.
Like, people love me."
That is, like, a façade
that you put up,
and I don't want that.
What I want is,
like, a real man
and an incredible man,
but that person has flaws
and can--and, like,
own up to them.
- I guess--I mean, yeah.
I mean, bottom line, I've been
trying to be too perfect...
And it has been hard for me,
especially the last few weeks
just because I feel like
I haven't had
the real you
that I met in the beginning.
And I feel like it's--I'm not
trying to put blame on you,
but I know that this has been
really hard for you, but I--
- Put some. I don't care.
Say what you feel.
- I feel like--okay.
Well, I feel like
it's been really hard
because of all these guys
saying things about me
that aren't true,
and I feel like it's just
really been hard for me
just to kind of, like,
let loose and be me.
- To be honest, the time that I
thought you were the most real
was the rugby date.
You [bleep] getting pissed
at Luke S. did not bother me.
Like, at least you were
showing some real emotion.
- Mm-hmm.
Well, I have
a question for you.
- What?
- When you were
on my side of this,
like, what helped you
just let go completely
of everything holding you back
from being completely
the real and raw you?
- Uh...
it honestly wasn't until I had
to deal with, like, real crap
that I had to...
drop everything.
I had never had a problem
with a girl in my entire life.
I'm not gonna say
everybody loved me,
but I've never,
like, had people
speak poorly of me so openly,
and I did not handle it well.
But it was through, like,
breaking down and, like,
realizing, like, "Holy crap,
I did this all wrong,"
where I really did start--
- Breaking those walls down.
- Breaking the walls down
but then just, like,
completely being myself.
- Well, I appreciate you
sharing that with me.
Um, I'm, like,
really mad at myself.
I don't want to come off
to you as, like,
I am truly trying
to be perfect in every way.
I'm just gonna be me
and I want you to know
when I'm being real and raw
and I feel like I have been,
but the last few weeks, I feel
like it's been tough for me
'cause there has been a lot
that's been said about me
that totally is fake
and not true,
so I have been
kind of fronting.
Like, look, that crap's fake.
It's not the truth,
because that is the truth.
- It's not about, like--like
I said, like, I make
my own decisions about people,
and I felt strongly that, like,
what people were saying was
not who you are to your core.
But then when I went to talk--
when I talked to you about it,
then I'm not feeling validated
and trusting myself in that
because it's just, like,
the same thing over and over.
You're not really, like...
You're just not really
saying anything.
You're not, like,
saying how you feel.
[whispers]
I don't know.
I just--
I wanna know, like,
what makes you mad,
like, what your relationship's
like with your dad,
like, has--like,
what has hurt you in the past
that you still
struggle with today?
Like, that's what I wanna know.
- You're making sense.
Um...
I'm doing my best to be
completely real with you,
and I wanna be
completely real with you.
But with the pressure
that I've been feeling
the last few weeks
of, oh, my gosh,
like, the woman of my dreams
is slipping out of my fingers,
like, I don't ever
want that feeling.
I want you to get the real me.
I want you to have the time
and the opportunity to.
And I feel like us getting
through all of this,
I know that it's gonna do
nothing but help us grow,
and I can genuinely look
you in the eyes and tell you
that I love every single thing
about you.
The way you've handled
everything--
- Uh, what?
- Yeah, even your flaws.
- Oh, God.
You think I'm,
like, this woman
that, like,
you've, like, dreamed of.
I'm like, "Are you sure?"
Because, like, I'm not perfect,
and I'm not putting on show.
- I know,
and I'm not perfect either.
- And so I don't
want that back.
And so I'm like, "Are you sure
this is what you want?"
Because, uh, there's, like,
this disconnect in that way.
Like, I just wanna make sure,
like, you understand that,
like, sometimes, I'm on
the front row at church, like,
with my knees on the ground
crying and praying.
And there's some times that
I'm a freakin' devilish bitch.
[pounds table]
- Yes.
- Okay, but, like, I want...
- I...
You have to, like,
love both of those.
- I am the same way.
- Well, you're not
owning up to that.
- Okay, well,
if there is something
that I do or say
or a trait that I have
that you don't think is okay,
I wanna know.
I don't think, right now,
I have any of those.
- Yeah, you do.
- A few.
- Yeah, you do
outside of that.
- One? This one we're--
- No, like, you do have flaws
and things
that are frustrating.
- Yeah, and I will be
mindful of those.
- Don't even be--
I mean, be mindful of them,
but just own up to 'em.
Don't say you don't.
You do.
I will not be
at the end of this
with somebody
who can't get past it.
But to get past it,
you have to own up to it.
[somber music]
I don't wanna be married
to somebody who thinks
that it's everybody else's
fault and can't take ownership,
and I don't want to have
a date and an experience
with somebody that's not real.
[dramatic music]
Luke stresses me because
I want so much more out of him
than he's giving me.
But he goes right back
to the weird, robotic Luke
that I have
no connection with.
It's just a round
and round circle
of just us not understanding
each other
and, like, me continually
trying to articulate that
in every way I could.
This is not going anywhere.
So I don't know, like,
what reason I have right now
to give Luke a rose.
♪ ♪
[crickets chirping]
- I'm tired
of "The Luke P. Show."
Ready to get that over with.
- I think
we're all ready for that.
- The Luke Ness Monster
fairy tale to be over.
is history, hopefully.
- When she does start
to question you
and she has that rose
on the table
and it's just you and her,
it's like, that's
when it's the most real.
I'd be lying if I said I
wasn't a little bit concerned
about how it's going for
Hannah tonight with Luke.
Only thing that I wish
is that the truth be told
and that she can see
the real Luke,
because if she sees
the Luke that we see,
he won't come back.
[dramatic music]
- I have not ever
experienced, um,
an initial, uh,
encounter with someone
for the first time
making me feel the way
that it was
when I first met you.
It wasn't just you.
But I feel like today, like,
I was trying as hard as I could
to express, like, what I needed
and, like, expressing
how I felt, but I wasn't
getting that in return,
and that's just, like,
very scary for me in this.
- Do you feel like you and I
had enough time today?
- Yeah, we had as much time
as any other date I've had.
- I don't know, I feel like
just the thought of everything
hurts me because all I want
for you is to have clarity,
and I feel like you
haven't had that with me.
- I gave you time to help give
me clarity, and you didn't.
And to be honest,
after today,
like, I didn't--
don't feel good.
- [sighs]
- And I don't know
how I feel about you.
♪ ♪
And all I want
is to see Luke be Luke.
But it's just not
what I...hoped for.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
I am always, good or bad,
excited to talk to you...
- That's very honest.
[chuckles]
- And want to know you more
and try and try for that
more than I have with anybody.
But, honestly, today was
the worst a day
has gone for me.
♪ ♪
With you, it's like, I see you,
but I want to, like,
see what's, like, under there,
like, the unseen
that you're not showing me
because, like, that is what
I want forever to be,
what I think's there.
But I didn't get to see it
today like I wanted to.
Like, this is not how
I pictured tonight going.
I didn't want to continue
talking about this.
I wanna know who you are,
and I don't.
I don't.
And sometimes I look at you
and I'm like,
"Yeah, I could totally see
you as my future husband,"
and sometimes I look at you
and I don't think that
there are any roads that,
like, lead to what I want,
like, what I really want.
Luke, I can't
give you this rose.
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
- Next week
on "The Bachelorette"...
- I'm so frustrated.
- I know I messed up.
- It sucks to see her
hurting right now.
I don't really know
where her head's at.
Guys here can't stop
throwing each other
under the bus.
- No one believes you.
Nobody believes you.
- What did you say, dude?
Just what did you say?
- Well, hold on. Hold on.
- Stop. I'm just,
like, really defeated
from all of you,
so I don't wanna do this.
[dramatic music]
[sobs]
- I need to know
that you're still in this
and you're capable
of being in this.
[dramatic music]
- It's my fault.
I hope that she forgives me.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Very cozy
for a first date, eh?
- Yep.
- Eh?
He's not been too familiar yet,
has he?
- Oh, room for Jesus.
I got three layers of pants on.
- Oh, that's good.
That's good.
My poetry is your passport
to continuous love,
so I'm Mike just now, okay?
- Okay.
- I wish I was Mike later on,
but I'm Mike just now.
- Oh.
[laughs]
- "O my love is like
a red, red rose
"that's newly sprung in June.
"O my love
is like the melody
"that's sweetly
played in tune.
"As fair art thou,
my bonny lass,
"so deep in love am I.
"And I will love thee still,
my dear,
till all the seas gang dry."
- Thank you so much, Mr. Willy.
- Thank you.
Bye-bye, bye-bye.
Cheers, cheers, cheers.
Here--
I'm not gonna kiss you.
- No, you get a hug.
- You're too tall.
You're too big, boy.
You're too--
You're a big boy, eh?
What size are your feet?
- 14.
- Oh, you'll have
a night tonight, my dear.
- Wow.
- Anyway...
[laughs]
- Oh, Lordy.
- Size 14, whoa-hoo.